

SOFTWARE ENGINEER, DEVELOPER, BACKEND PROGRAMMER

#### **Details**

San Jose, 95138 United States 4088571993

brandon.maz@mail.com

02/08/1983

#### Links

Portfolio

<u>GitHub</u>

Linkedin

**Storefront Project** 

Yelp Project

Todo Project

WaterCooler Project

#### Skills

Python

**JavaScript** 

HTML & CSS

React

**React Native** 

MySQL

Ruby

Ruby on Rails

MongoDB

Node.js

jQuery

Bootstrap

Git

Heroku

## **Hobbies**

Ceramics, Cycling, SpaceX, Gaming, Board Games, Car Enthusiast, Programming, Creating a kids learning app with React Native

## **Profile**

Software Engineer with 12+ years experience in customer service. Natural ability to promote products and build rapport through listening and communication skills. Well rounded individual in oral communication and experience with working in groups. Energetic self-starter with strong communication skills; work well independently or on a team. Ambitious, flexible team member who loves to learn. Skilled problem-solver and multi-tasker.

# **Employment History**

#### Deputy Sheriff, Santa Clara County Sheriff's, Santa Clara

FEBRUARY 2019 - JUNE 2020

- Demonstrating the ability to learn quickly, adapt to dynamic situations and deliver consistent quality in job duties.
- Displaying a commitment to the department through participation in ongoing professional development
- Overseeing the main prison population, diffusing potentially volatile situations and maintaining the safety of inmates and prison staff

#### Fitness Coach, Mint Condition Fitness, Los Gatos

FEBRUARY 2017 - NOVEMBER 2018

- Collaborating with other fitness instructors in matters pertinent to client oversight
- Managed client's scheduling and their workout routines

#### Brandon's Cross Fitness Training, Self Employed, Los Gatos

FEBRUARY 2007 - FEBRUARY 2016

- Controlled my own schedule and managed time very well
- Worked with other independent trainers. Acquired and maintained clientele

## **Education**

#### Software Engineer, General Assembly, Online

NOVEMBER 2020 - FEBRUARY 2021

#### AS Sports Medicine, Gavilan College

MARCH 2012 - MAY 2016

## AA Communications, West Valley College

AUGUST 2001 - MAY 2004

## **Courses**

#### **Software Engineer Immersive, General Assembly**

NOVEMBER 2020 - FEBRUARY 2021

#### **POST, Santa Clara County**

MARCH 2019 - NOVEMBER 2019

## **Projects**

#### **Storefront Project**

Javascript, Mongoose, Express, Node, jQuery and Bootstrap

## Yelp Project

Javascript, MERN stack with one other developer

#### **Todo Project**

JavaScript, Ruby and React with 3 other developers

## WaterCooler Project

MERN stack with 3 other developers and a UX/UI team